http://www.mioot.com/privacy_policy/

miOOt live chat is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of live chat visitors to our web sites as well as the privacy of our actual customer’s data.
What information do we collect?
When you visit our web site www.mioot.com , our web server collects basic user information about you that includes your ISP’s domain, the time you accessed our web site, and the pages from within our web site that you visit.
When you sign up for mioot’s services, you provide us with both contact and payment information. Contact information typically includes your name, address and phone number. Payment information typically includes your credit card number.
Onbehalf of customer we may collect first name , last name email and other contact details and it vary customer to customer. Also we will collect and store the chat messages for our customer’s future reference and analatical purpose.
How do we use this information?
The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze web traffic and to improve the content of our web site.
The data collected from the customer will be used only for mioot’s internal purpose to establish our service for you. We use payment information for payment processing purposes only. We create and maintain other information such as customer account status, choice of services and customer logs in the normal course of providing a service. miOOt may share customer information with selected partners/third parties to provide you with information about products that might be of interest to you or to enable you to take advantage of special partner programs.
All the data collected on behalf the customer is used only for the that perticular customer and we process this data to genearte the reports for the benifit of the customer.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a piece of information that our Web site sends to your browser, which then stores this information on your system. If a cookie is used, our Web site will be able to “remember” information about you and your preferences either until you exit your current browser window (if the cookie is temporary) or until you disable or delete the cookie . We use cookies to store vistor Id , Session id and customer information inorder to identify the frequent visitor and their needs.
Disclosure to Third Parties
To serve you better, we use information provided by you to perform services that you request. Although we never sell any information to third parties/business affiliates, we may provide personal data to other parties that perform certain functions for us, such as service installation, or to other parties that provide products with our services so that you may obtain service on your product. These third parties are required to only use the information in connection with the requested services.
We will not otherwise disclose customer personal and account information unless we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of mioot , our customers, or others, or where mioot has good belief that the law requires such disclosure.
Security
miOOt live chat is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
If miOOt live chat software decide to change the privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us online or by mail at privacy@mioot.com
